The average person uses 10% of their brain capacity.
Imagine what she could do with 100%.
Lucy is a action, science fiction film directed by Luc Besson.
A woman, accidentally caught in a dark deal, turns the tables on her captors and
transforms into a merciless warrior evolved beyond human logic.
Lucy, played by Scarlett Johansson.
Professor Norman, played by Morgan Freeman.
Mr. Jang, played by Choi Min-sik.
Pierre Del Rio, played by Amr Waked.
The Limey, played by Julian Rhind-Tutt.
Richard, played by Pilou Asbæk.
Lucy is a 2014 English-language French science fiction action film written and directed by Luc
Besson for his company EuropaCorp, and produced by his wife, Virginie Besson-Silla.
It was shot in Taipei, Paris, and New York City.
It stars Scarlett Johansson, Morgan Freeman, Choi Min-sik, and Amr Waked.
Johansson portrays Lucy, a woman who gains psychokinetic abilities when a
nootropic, psychedelic drug is absorbed into her bloodstream.
The film was released on 25 July 2014 and became a massive box office success, grossing over
$469 million worldwide, more than eleven times the budget of $40 million.
It received generally positive, but also polarized, critical reviews.
Although praise was given for its themes, visuals, and Johansson's performance, many critics found the plot
nonsensical, especially its focus on the ten-percent-of-the-brain myth and resulting abilities.
The film explores themes of artificial intelligence (a.i.),
telepathy, intelligence, drug mule, time travel.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.